〈（梨穂子）２年前の１２月〉
Two years ago, in December...
〈私は　幼なじみの純一から〉
My childhood friend Junichi suddenly invited me to go shopping with him.
〈突然　買い物に誘われました〉
〈もう　すっごくうれしくて
デート気分で出かけたら〉
I was overjoyed and left the house thinking it was a date.
〈実は　純一が好きな女の子に贈る
クリスマスプレゼント選びに〉
However, Junichi just wanted me to help him
choose a Christmas present for the girl he liked.
〈つきあわされただけ
だったんです〉
〈私　がっかりしちゃって…〉
I was kinda disappointed...
〈プレゼント選びは　それはそれで〉
I did have a lot of fun choosing the present though.
〈とても
楽しかったんですけどね〉
〈でも　結局　その子と純一は
うまくはいかなかったみたいで〉
But it looked like things didn't go well for Junichi and the girl in the end.
〈後から　それを知ったときは〉
When I learned about it later, I felt
as bad as if it had happened to me.
〈自分のことみたいに
悲しくなっちゃいました〉
〈あの頃も今も〉
Back then, and even now...
〈私は　ずっと純一に〉
My love for Junichi has always been one-sided.
〈片思い中なんです〉
・～
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたら
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
何度も季節を重ねたね　あの日から
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
今日までどうもありがとう
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
狭い路地裏目指し
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
白い息が踊る
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
痛いくらい握った手をひいて
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
君は進んでいく
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
今すぐキスしたかった
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
隠れた自販機の裏
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
ハニかんで見つめあった
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
優しいキモチ溢れた
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたなら
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
２人は１つだよ
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
どんな小さな幸せも
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
見つけ出せる気がするよ
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
優しくなれたのは　君のおかげ
（目覚まし）
Graduation Ceremony
Ceremonial Hall
（目覚まし）
（香苗）桜井！
Sakurai!
遅刻するよ！
You're gonna be late!
It's so cold...
寒いよ
あんた　ダンゴムシか
What are you, a pill bug?
何で
目覚まし鳴らなかったんだろう？
Why didn't my alarm go off?
Your alarm did go off, loud and clear!
（香苗）ガンガン鳴り響いてたよ
目覚まし
えッ　ホントに？
Huh?  Really?
Yeah.
うん
はあ…
よかった
香苗ちゃんが迎えに来てくれて
I'm glad you came to get me, Kanae-chan.
まったく　世話が焼けるわね
Geez, you're really troublesome.
それにしても
最近　遅刻多すぎだよ
At any rate, you're late way too often these days.
えへへ…　あッ！　いけない忘れ物
Oh no!  I forgot something!
えーッ！
取ってくる
I'm going back to get it!
あッ　今日　日直だった
えッ？
Wait, I'm on cleaning duty today!
どうしよう　どうしよう
私が日直の仕事代わるから
What do I do?  What do I do?!
Well, I'll fill in for you today.
早く取っておいで
Quick, go back and get it!
Really?
本当？
Okay!
うん！
うわッ！
Sakurai Rihoko Arc
Chapter 1
Memories
はあ　はあ　はあ…
〈うわあ
正門まで回ってる時間ないなあ〉
I don't have enough time to make it through the main gate.
〈よ～し〉
All right!
はあ　はあ…
よいしょっと…
うッ　あれ？
Huh?
う～ん　うーッ　ぐぐ…
ふーッん！
引いてダメなら押して…　うん？
If I can't pull myself through... I'll push!
No way!
うそ！　ふんッ　グググ
ふん！　グググ…
えッ　えッ？
Huh?  What?!
うッ　すみません！
I-I'm sorry!
ちょっと近道しようと
思っただけなんです～
I was just trying to take a shortcut!
今朝　うっかり忘れ物して
I accidentally forgot something at home this morning, and...
それで　その　取りに戻って
Uh... I went back to get it...
あの…　ごめんなさい！
I'm really sorry!
今すぐ抜けますから～
（純一）落ち着け　梨穂子　僕だよ
I'll come out right away!
Calm down, Rihoko.  It's me.
えッ　純一？
Huh?  Junichi?
Junichi, is that you?
純一なの？
ああ
Yeah.
Waah, Junichi!
ふえ～　純一～
何してるんだよ？
それが　その…
What are you doing?
I'm... uh...
Don't tell me... you're stuck?
まさか　抜けないのか？
エへへへ　当たり～
Bingo...
Then I guess I'll have to make a dash to the gate.
じゃッ　僕は正門までダッシュする
せいぜい　後は頑張ってくれ
Best of luck to you.
えーッ　そんなあ
Huh?!
No way!
長いつきあいだったが
こんな別れ方するなんてな
We've been friends for so long, but who would've thought we'd part like this?
成仏しろよ　梨穂子！
May you rest in peace, Rihoko!
No!  Don't abandon me!
イヤ～ッ！　見捨てちゃイヤだよ
ハハハハ…　冗談だよ
I'm just kidding.
バカ！
You jerk!
ごめん　ごめん
I'm sorry.
今　助けてやるから　あんま怒るな
I'll get you out of there, so don't get so mad.
Relax your body and lie flat.
体の力を抜いて　うつぶせになれ
うん…
Whoa, wait.
あッ　待って
なッ　何だよ？
What now?
見えて…　ない？
何が？
Can you... see?
See what?
その…
Um...
Pa... Pan...
パ…　パン…
パン？
Pan?
Come on now, you're thinking about pancakes at a time like this?
おいおい　こんな時にも食い気か？
パンツ　見えてない！？
Can you see my panties?!
見えてないよ
I can't.
そッ　そう…
I see...
じゃあ
Okay then.
Ready?  I'll pull now.
いいか？　引っ張るぞ
うん
Okay.
ふんッ　わ～ッ！
きゃーッ
I-Idiot!  Don't make noises like that!
バッ　バカ！　何て声　出すんだ
だって　胸が引っかかって…
But my chest got caught...
Huh?  You sure it wasn't your belly?
はあ？　腹の間違いだろ
It's not!
違うもん
いいから　もう一度いくぞ
Whatever, let's try again.
せーの！
One, two!
ふにゃ～
おッ？
助かった　バンザーイ！
I'm out!  Hooray!
うわ～ッ
あッ！
うん？
ああ！
A-Are you okay?
だッ　大丈夫？
まったく
また体重　増えたんじゃないのか？
Geez... did you put on weight again?
What?!
え～ッ！？
だから　通れないんだよ
That's why you couldn't get through.
ううん　これは　きっと
着膨れだよ
No, I'm sure it's because I'm wearing a lot today!
このコートのせいじゃないかなあ
I wonder if it's because of this coat.
いや　食べすぎだろ
えッ？
Nope, it's because you eat too much.
（チャイム）
I've gotta run!
あッ　急がなくちゃ
純一？
Junichi?
梨穂子も急げよ
Rihoko, you should hurry too.
えッ　え～ッ？
えッ…
（ホイッスル）
やーッ
あッ！
うう…
So your PE uniform was what you forgot?
忘れ物って体操服だったの？
うん
Yeah.
でも　橘君もひどいよね
Wasn't Tachibana-kun kinda a jerk though?  Leaving you behind like that...
自分だけ先に行っちゃうなんて
ううん　そんなことないよ
No, not at all.
純一が来てくれなかったら
あそこに挟まったまま
If Junichi hadn't come for me, I'd probably spend the rest of my life stuck there.
一生を
終えるところだったんだから
Uh, I highly doubt that...
いや　いくらなんでも　それは…
I've always made it through that hole before.
前は　あの穴
ちゃんと抜けられたのにな
やっぱり最近　太ったかも
Maybe I really did get fatter recently.
ふうん
Is it because I eat too much?
食べすぎかなあ？
そうだね
Maybe...
ねえ　エアダイエットっていうのは
どうかな？
Hey, why don't you try the Air Diet?
えッ　エアダイエット？
Huh?  Air Diet?
うん　食べたいなって思ったら
Yeah, when you feel like eating something, you go like this...
こうやって
食べたふりをして　思いっきり
空気を吸い込んでおくの
And take in a deep breath of air while pretending you just ate it.
Ooh, I see.
へえ　なるほど
うーん
うん　明日からやってみるよ
あは…
Yup, I'll try it tomorrow!
Oh yeah, you also need to exercise after eating.
あッ　それとさ
食べたら運動しなきゃ
運動？
Exercise?
Here it comes, Hibiki!
（はるか）いくよ　響→
Catch it like a puppy!
ワンちゃんみたいにキャッチしてね
（響）何それ？
いくよ！
What's that supposed to mean?
Here I go!
Ah!  Sorry!
あッ　ごめん
あッ
Watch out!
・（響）危ない！
きゃー！
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
Yes, it's okay!
はい　大丈夫です
ごめんなさい　大丈夫？
Sorry!  Are you okay?
えへへへ　平気です　はい
It's fine, yes.
Here you go.
はい　どうぞ
（響）ありがとう
Thanks.
I'm really sorry about that.
本当に　ごめんなさいね
Don't worry, it wasn't harmed at all.
いえ　大丈夫でしたから
How nice.  They both have have great figures.
いいなあ　２人ともスタイルがよくて
運動は　やっぱり大事なんだね
I guess exercise really is important.
私も明日から　ちゃんとしよう
I'll start doing that tomorrow too!
でも　何でまた　ダイエット復活なの？→
But why are you starting a diet again?
この前は　もういいって
言ってたじゃない
Didn't you say you were done with them?
《いや　食べすぎだろ》
《はッ》
Nope, it's because you eat too much.
えっと　別に
Well... uh...
There's no real... reason.
特に理由は…　ないよ
はは～ん　さては橘君に
何か言われたんでしょう？
So did Tachibana-kun say something to you?
純一は全然関係ないよ
Junichi has nothing to do with this.
はいはい　バレバレだよ
Yeah, right.  It's written all over your face.
違うもん…
You're wrong...
Actually, I think I'll start today!
やっぱり　今日から頑張る！
穴　通れるくらいスマートになる
I'll slim down enough to fit through that hole!
If you weren't so late all the time, you wouldn't need that hole-
遅刻しなければ
穴を通らなくてもいい
よーし　やるぞーッ！
All right, I'm gonna do it!
あッ　香苗ちゃん　食べる？
Kanae-chan, do you want this?
私はもう　おなかいっぱいだよ
I'm already full.
あッ　ひらめいた
Oh, I know!
おい　梅原
Hey, Umehara.
（梅原）うん　大将？→
Boss, what's up?
どうした？
これ…
This...
ありがとな
Thanks bud.
So how was it?
（小声で）で　どうだった？
Now I understand why you kept recommending it.
やたらと薦めてくれた理由が
よーく分かったよ
（梅原）ちなみに
どの子が　お気に入りだ？
So which girl did you like best?
そうだな～　後ろの方に載ってた
ピンクのビキニを着た
Let's see...
That girl in the back with the pink bikini and short hair.
ショートカットの子かな？
結構　ぽっちゃり系の…
She's a little chubby...
ふうん　あの子か
That girl, huh?
そういえば　あの子
Now that you mention it, doesn't she kinda look like Sakurai-san?
ちょっと
桜井さんに似てなかったか？
え～ッ　そうかあ！？
Huh?  You think so?!
シーッ！　声がデカイぞ　大将
Keep your voice down, boss.
えッ！
（詞）２人とも　日本史のプリント
まだよね？
Neither of you have submitted your Japanese History assignments yet.
もうできているなら
出してくれるかな
Can you turn them in if you're done with them?
あッ　ああ
すぐ出すよ
Yeah!  Right away!
じゃあ　お願いね
Okay, I'd appreciate it.
はあ～
Junichi!
純一！
Rihoko.
梨穂子
くれるのか？
うん
These are for me?
Yeah.
Well, they're kinda like a thank-you for this morning.
あのね　今朝のお礼っていうか私…
And I'm...
ダイエットすることにしたから
...gonna go on a diet!
て　そのセリフ　もう耳に
タコが　できるほど聞いてるぞ
Right.  And I've heard you say that so many times that I'll probably go deaf.
今回は　ちゃんと
頑張るつもりなんだよ～
I'm gonna try really hard this time!
はいはい　で　本当は自分で
食べるつもりだったおやつを
Yeah, right.
So you're giving me the treats
you originally made for yourself?
僕に食べろと
How did you know?
何で分かるの？
いいよ　もらうよ
Sure, I'll take them.
今朝のことで
ちょっと潰れちゃってるけど
They're a little beat up from this morning, but I'm pretty confident about them.
自信作なんだよ
I'm sure they'll taste great since you made them, Rihoko.
梨穂子の手作りなら　味は
間違いないもんな　サンキュー
Thank you.
Hey, Tachibana-kun.
ねえ　橘君さ　今度の日曜日　ヒマ？
うん？
Are you free this Sunday?
香苗ちゃん？
Huh?
Kanae-chan?
Sakurai and I were talking about doing some sports together.
桜井と何か
スポーツしようって話してたんだけど
Wanna join us?  Skating or something.
一緒にどう？　スケートとか
えッ　そんな話…
Huh?  When did we-
Skating?
スケート？
（香苗）梅原君も　どう？
Umehara-kun, wanna come too?
おッ　おお　喜んで！
Oh, I'd love to.
Boss, you're coming too, right?
大将も　いいだろう？
えっと…
Uh...
Okay, it's decided!
よ～し　決まりだ！
ありがとう！
Thanks!
香苗ちゃん？
じゃッ　日曜日
Kanae-chan?
Well, see you on Sunday!
Why'd you ask them to go skating?
急にスケートって　どういうこと？
It's fine, it's fine.
いいから　いいから
Panda Cocoa
うう…
（ボタンを押す）
oolong tea
はあ…
ああ　ごめんなさい
（逢）いえ→
Ah, I'm sorry!
No worries.
ねえ　何にする？
So what are you getting?
（紗江）私　パンダココアにしよう
I'm getting a Panda Cocoa.
（逢）それ　ちょっと
病みつきになる味だよね
That has a pretty addictive flavor.
But it has a lot of calories.
（紗江）でもカロリー高そう
太っちゃうかなあ
I wonder if it'll make me fat.
（逢）大丈夫じゃない？
I think you'll be fine.
PERSISTENCE
YIELDS
RESULTS
Senpai, there's something I want to tell you-
先輩　ちょっと　お話が
・（琉璃子）おッ　りほっち
いいところに来たね
Ooh, Rihocchi.  Good timing.
Huh?
Ah, it's the choux crème from the bakery at the train station!
あッ　駅前のパティスリーのシュークリーム！
Bingo.
（愛歌）当たり
ああ…
めくるめくカスタード　真実のチョコレート
That's Dazzling Custard.
And that's True Chocolate.
すご～い　おいしそうですね
Wow!  They look delicious.
（琉璃子）誰も取ったりしないから
好きな方から食べなよ
Nobody's gonna take them from you, so eat as much as you want.
Dig in.
召し上がれ
じゃあ　カスタードから
I'll start with a custard one!
いっただっきまーす
Here I go!
It's delicious!
おいしい
りほっち　シュークリームの語源って
知ってるかい？
Rihocchi, do you know the etymology for the word "choux crème"?
No, I don't.
いいえ　知りませんけど
In ancient Hebrew, "shook" stood for "love", and "lim" meant "charm".
古代ヘブライ語で
「シューク」は「愛」
「リーム」には
「おまじない」って意味があってね
Really?
へえ～
・（琉璃子）もともとは→
It was originally a treat you'd give to
someone you like when proposing to them.
好きな人にプロポーズするときに
渡したお菓子なんだってさ
You'd do well to remember that.
・（愛歌）覚えておくといい
はい
Yes.
りほっち　ほっぺほっぺ
えッ？
Rihocchi, your cheek.
Huh?
違う違う　右側
あッ
Not that side.  Your right cheek.
There's more.
まだあるよ
えッ　いいんですか？
Can I really have more?
ああ
成長期
Yeah.
You're a growing girl.
I guess I'll have a chocolate one this time.
じゃあ　今度はチョコにしようかな
あッ　そういえば
話って何だったんだい？
By the way, what did you want to tell us earlier?
Ah, I've decided to go on a diet.
ああ　私
ダイエットすることにしたんです
Rihocchi, you...
りほっち　あんた…
うん？
わッ！　あっと　えっと
Ah!  I, uh...
Looks like it won't go well this time either.
（琉璃子）今回もダメそうだね
Um... I'm starting tomorrow...
えっと　始めるのは明日からで…
So having it today means I'm barely safe...
だから今日は　ぎりぎりセーフで…
うう　失礼します！
E-Excuse me!
（戸が閉まる）
Geez, she's such an innocent girl.
まったく　どこまでも素直な子だよ
シュークリームの語源
About the etymology for "choux crème".
ふふふ…　ああ　あれ
Ah yes, about that.
確か本当はフランス語で
「シュー・ア・ラ・クレーム」だっけ？
Didn't the word come from the French "choux à la crème"?
そう　「クリーム入りのキャベツ」という意味
Yes.  It means "cabbage with cream inside".
信じちゃってたな　りほっち
Rihocchi fell for it.
ういやつ
Poor girl.
（琉璃子）にしても３年の私らが
卒業したら→
Though, what's gonna happen to the Tea Club once we seniors graduate?
茶道部は　どうなるんだ？→
３人しかいないしな
There's only the three of us.
・（愛歌）りほっち１人じゃ
先行き不安
I'm worried for the future of the club with just Rihocchi.
Actually, without other club members, this club'll have to disband.
というか　りほっち以外の部員が
いないと　廃部になっちゃうよ
The club is in danger.
存続危機
はあ…
（薫）ちょっと　お２人さん！
Wait, you two!
I don't have to go to my part-time job today.
私　今日はバイト休みだからさ
久々にビリヤードとか　どう？
We haven't played billiards in a while, so how about it?
悪いな　薫
Sorry, Kaoru.
今日は用事がある
We have business to take care of today.
Huh?  What business?
えッ　用事って何？
I can wait for you guys if it's quick.
すぐ終わるなら
待っててもいいわよ
いや　今日の用事は
そう簡単には終わらない
Nope.
Today's business won't be taken care of that easily.
なッ　梅原？
ああ
Right, Umehara?
Yeah.
何よ　それ？
Huh?  What's that mean?
男には
男の事情ってものがあるんだ
We men have our own problems to take care of.
それ以上は踏み込むな　薫
You shouldn't pry in any further, Kaoru.
行くぞ　梅原
Let's go, Umehara.
おう　すまんな　棚町
Yeah.
Sorry, Tanamachi.
ヘンなの
Weirdos.
ていうか　怪しい
Actually, something isn't right.
Hey, so what do you have in return for lending you that book?
・（梅原）おい
本のお礼って何だよ？
へっへへ　驚くなよ～
Try to stay calm.
これだ！
This is it!
This is a collection of drawings.
このデッサン集なんだが
A treasure among treasures.  I was so surprised!
これが　とんでもないお宝だって
いうんだから　びっくりだぞ
まさか　学校の図書室にある
代物が？
You're kidding!  This was something you found at the school library?
ああ　そのまさかなんだよ
この中の…
Yeah, that's exactly right.  This one right here-
みなまで言うな　大将！
Stop right there, boss!
Whoops, I accidentally raised my voice.
と　思わず声がデカくなっちまった
うわッ！
Rihoko?
梨穂子？
ダイエット宣言した手前
誰にも見つからないように
Right before you begin your diet,
you hide where nobody can see you and have a choux crème.
あそこでシュークリーム食べてたって
お前…
You...
えへへ…
Well, you'll probably give up right away.
どうせ　すぐやめるんだろ？
ひどいよ～
That's mean.
I'll definitely succeed this time!
今度こそ成功させるんだから
何でまた
ダイエットする気になったんだ？
Why are you going on a diet again?
おッ　それは…　それは…
Well... I...
えっと…
Um...
まッ　宣言したからには頑張れよな
Well, you should try harder since you said you'd do it.
僕も応援するよ
I'll be rooting for you too.
久しぶりだね
純一と一緒に帰るの
It's been so long since the last time we walked home together.
えッ？　そうだったかな
Huh?  Really?
ここ通ると
子供の頃のこと思い出すね
Walking past here brings back childhood memories.
うん？
ほら　あの滑り台
Like that slide.
ねえ　幼稚園の頃だっけ？
うん？
Hey, was it during kindergarten?
Huh?
ほら　純一が魔法で…
Remember?  You used magic, and...
《ルンルン　ルンルン　ルルルリラ～》
《お姫様になれ
きれいなお姫様になれ～》
Become a princess.
Become a beautiful princess!
《ルンルン　ルンルン　ルルルリラ～》
《お姫様になれ
きれいなお姫様になれ～》
Become a princess.
Become a beautiful princess!
《（美也）お姫様　お姫様　にしし…》
A princess, a princess!
《ルンルン　ルンルン…》
覚えてない？　私をお姫様に
変身させてくれるって遊び
Don't you remember?
You were trying to turn me into a princess.
I was?
遊び？　ああ　あれか
Oh, you mean that.
うん？　お姫様だっけ？
Huh?  Was it really a princess?
《マンマ　マンマン　ママンガマン》
《おいしそうな
まんま肉まんになれ～》
Become a delicious meat bun!
《マンマ　マンマン　ママンガマン》
《おいしそうな
まんま肉まんになれ～》
A meat bun, a meat bun!
《まんま肉まん　まんま肉まん
にししし…》
《まんま肉まん　まんま肉まん…》
A meat bun, a meat bun!
We often played here when we were kids, didn't we?
小さい頃
ここでよく遊んだもんね
なつかしいな～
It brings back memories.
うん　そうだな
Yeah.  I agree.
純一　いくよ～
Junichi, here I go!
気をつけろよ
それ～
Careful now!
ググッ！
（美也）何？→
What?
Onii-chan and Riho-chan?
お兄ちゃん　梨穂ちゃん？
お兄ちゃん　梨穂ちゃ…
Onii-chan, Riho-cha-
Miya.
美也
エヘヘヘ…
My butt's stuck.
お尻　挟まっちゃって
（３人）ハッ　ハハハ…
うッ　増えてる
No, I gained weight!
ああ　そうか　タオルが重いんだ
Ah, must be because the towel's heavy.
あれ？　あんまり変わらない
Huh?
It didn't change very much.
う～ん
I need to get rid of this...
これが取れちゃえばなあ
よーし　頑張ろ～っと
All right, I'll do my best!
うッ　ううう…
I-I'm so stiff...
かッ　硬いな～
よッ　イタタタ…
Ow...
はあ…
It's a lot harder than I thought.
結構　大変かも
Maybe I'll try for real starting tomorrow.
本格的にやるのは　明日からだなあ
I should be well on time today.
今日は余裕だな…　っと
ああ　また遅刻しちゃう
Ah, I'm gonna be late again!
Why does staying in bed feel so good?
何で　あんなにお布団の中って
気持ちいいのかなあ？
うう
I'll be late if I don't use this.
〈ここを通らないと遅刻しちゃう〉
よいしょっと
引っかからないで…　うッ
Please don't get stuck...
あれ？
Huh?
I got through...
抜けた…
抜けた～！
I got through!
《うッ　うーーん》
Rihoko should've been able to get through that this morning.
〈梨穂子のやつ
今日は通れたはずだよな〉
All I did yesterday was a few stretches!
昨日　ストレッチ
ちょっとやっただけなんだよ
（香苗）へえ～　そうなの？→
Oh?  Really?
That's good.
よかったじゃない
うん
Yeah!
I get the feeling my diet'll work this time!
今度こそ
ダイエット成功する気がする！
Yep!
うん！
Kokoro ga kyunto
心がきゅんと
The area around my heart tightens
・～
Sukoshi dake kyunto
少しだけきゅんと
Just a little bit
Shimetsukerareta nara
締め付けられたなら
Since it's tightening like this
Hontou no koi na no kana?
本当の恋なのかな？
Could this be true love?
Hikaru shibafu no ue
光る芝生の上
Didn't we use to play around
Fuzakete nekoronda ne
ふざけて寝転んだね
And lie down on the sunlit grass?
Mujaki datta
無邪気だった
We were so innocent
Osanakatta hibi
幼かった日々
During our childhood days
Demo kokoro no oku de
でも心の奥で
But deep in my heart
Sodatte yuku kanjou wo
育って行く感情を
A feeling was growing
Sukoshi zutsu kizukihajimeteta
少しずつ気づき始めてた
And I slowly came to realize it
Onaji toki wo sugoshita bun dake
同じ時を過ごした分だけ
The more time we spent together
Sunao ni narenakute
素直になれなくて
The less able I was to be honest
Toomawari shita
遠回りした
I did things indirectly
Kokoro de gyutto
心でぎゅっと
My heart tightens
Tonari de sotto dakishimete
隣でそっと抱き締めて
As you gently embrace me
Anata wo mitsumeteru yo
あなたを見つめてるよ
I can't take my eyes off you
Sore wa chiisana koi no hajimari
それは小さな恋の始まり
That's the beginning of this small love of mine
Ima wa mada ienai kedo
今はまだ言えないけど
I can't tell you this just yet
Anata ga suki da yo
あなたが好きだよ
But I love you
Preview
N-Next episode preview!
Amazing, Sakurai!
They're letting you do the preview!
Yeah, I'm apparently the protagonist.
By the way, you shouldn't use that hole in the fence too much.
Why, Kanae-chan?
I mean, you'll scratch your knees and get your clothes dirty.
As a girl, you can't be looking like that in the morning!
Oh, I see...
Next episode: "Help".
Next Episode
Help
I wonder if Junichi'll dislike me for that.
You really are troublesome.